houseofaceonline.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [houseofaceonline@gmail.com](mailto:houseofaceonline@gmail.com).

At www.houseofaceonline.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by www.houseofaceonline.com and how we use it.

On our website, we run several third-party services and use cookies to optimise your browsing experience.

Cookies

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.

Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track and analyze our web traffic. We do not have access to the information collected by Google apart from what is displayed in our Google Analytics portal.

We have implemented the following data collection features in Google Analytics:

1\. Remarketing with Google AdSense

Enables data collection for Display and Search Remarketing. This includes data from Google’s signed-in users who have chosen to enable Google to associate their web and app browsing history with their Google account, and to use such information from their Google account to personalize ads. Google Analytics temporarily joins these identifiers to your Google Analytics data in order to support your audiences. When you enable this setting, you must adhere to the Google Analytics Advertising Features Policy, including rules around sensitive categories and the necessary privacy disclosures to your end users about the data you collect and share with Google.

2\. Advertising Reporting Features

Enables Advertising Reporting features like Audience Demographics and Interests Reporting, DoubleClick Campaign Manager reporting, DoubleClick Bid Manager reporting, and Google Display Network Impression Reporting that help you better understand your users.

The information collected by Google may be linked to your Google account if you’re signed in. Google may also collect information relating to your:

• browsing device;

• location;

• operating system.

Please read Google’s Privacy Policy for more information on how your data is collected and used: https://policies.google.com/privacy

To opt out of Google’s data collection, you may also set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services.

Google Adsense

We display advertisement powered by Google Adsense. Google Adsense uses the information Google collects to display the most useful ads online. When you’re signed in to your Google Account, they will also collect information that they store with your Google account. We do not have access to any data collected by Google for the purposes of advertising.

You may choose to opt out of personalised advertisements by disabling cookies.

WordPress comments

If you choose to comment on our site, you will be asked to provide a name and email address. The data which you provide and your comment will be stored on our server along with your public IP address.

Email/newsletter

When subscribing to our email newsletter, you may be asked to enter your name and/or email address or other details to help you with your experience.

As a newsletter subscriber, we keep a record of your IP address, the emails you open, and the links you click within those emails, so that we can more accurately recommend content, occasional third party offers and products that you might find valuable.

Any personal information you provide to us, including and similar to your name and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of houseofaceonline.com. However, if you participate in a competition, your email address might be provided to the relevant vendor for registration/activation and ongoing support purposes.

We will never ask for credit card details and request that you do not enter them on any of the forms on houseofaceonline.com.

To remove your data from our email server, simply unsubscribe through any one of our emails.

Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website or in our newsletter. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page.

How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?

It’s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur we will notify you via email within 7 business days.

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

Last updated: 21 May 2018

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

houseofaceonline.com

houseofaceonline@gmail.com
